# Eky Galih Gunanda

Fullstack Web Developer | Software Engineer | Network Engineer

ekygalihgunandaa@gmail.com

### Introduction

☐ Hi. I'm Eky. I am a software engineer. I have worked in this field for approximately 4 + years, focusing on web development as a back end or front end. Currently, I am using Python and Go on the backend and VueJs on the front end.

I also like learning new skills and reading is my hobby.

• Mataram, Mataram City, West Nusa Tenggara, Indonesia

in <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/ekyga">https://github.com/EkyGalih</a>

## Experience

Network Engineer • Badan Pengelolaan Keuangan

responsible for network security and office network management

Sep 2020 - Present

### Full Stack Web Developer • Universitas Islam Al

- Developed the INGES app
- find and fix bug

Sep 2020 - Dec2021

### Software Engineer • Bumi Nusantara

- create a SIAKAD application and become part of the INGES system
- find and fix bug
- Develop API for processing data using RESTfull
- responsible for monitoring the siakad system

#### PT. Netzen Media Akses

Jan 2020 - Dec 2021

## Full Stack Developer • Kota Mataram

- build a Point of System program
- find and fix bug
- develop API for ordering and transaction processing
- deploy the app to domain and hosting

April 2019 - March 2020

#### Education



2013 - 2018

### Universitas Bumigora

Bachelor's of Engineering Computer Science

#### Skills

- Web Development
- JavaScript
- Front End
- Back End
- Python
- JQuery
- · Transaction Processing
- Ordering
- API
- · Fullstack Web Developer
- Linux System Administration
- · Python Programming
- · Network Engineering

## Project

Aug 2020 - Dec 2021

#### Siakad

academic information system

Sep 2020 - Dec 2021

#### **INGES**

Al Azhar Islamic University College Information SystemUniversitas Islam Al Other Skills

• Language: Fluent in English and Indonesian.

SIAKAD is a system for student curriculum management, making KRS and KRS, making lecture schedules, and many other features.

INGES is a higher education information system that was developed for the Academic Environment of Al Azhar Islamic University Mataram. Applications developed include:

- 1. New Student Admission System
- 2. Financial System
- 3. Academic Information System
- 4. Inventory System

Jan 2020 - Dec 2021

## **Expert System**

Scholarship Admission System with C45. method

an application made to help universities to select suitable students for scholarships using the C45 method

April 2019 - Maret 2020

#### Website BPKAD NTB

Information Systems

rebuilt the information system of local government agencies for Financial and Asset Management and changed the programming language used from python flask to python django.